♪ Born of cold and winter air ♪
♪ And mountain rain combining ♪
♪ This icy force both foul and fair ♪
♪ Has a frozen heart worth mining ♪
♪ So cut through the heart ♪
♪ Cold and clear ♪
♪ Strike for love and strike for fear ♪
<font color="
♪ Split the ice apart ♪
♪ And break the frozen heart
Hyup, ho! ♪
♪ Watch your step
Let it go ♪
♪ Hyup, ho! ♪
♪ Watch your step
Let it go ♪
♪ -Beautiful
-Powerful ♪
<font color="
-Cold ♪
♪ Ice has a magic
Can't be controlled ♪
♪ Stronger than one ♪
♪ Stronger than ten ♪
♪ Stronger than a hundred men! ♪
Oh!
♪ Born of cold and winter air ♪
♪ And mountain rain combining ♪
<font color="
♪ Has a frozen heart worth mining ♪
♪ Cut through the heart ♪
♪ Cold and clear ♪
♪ Strike for love and strike for fear ♪
♪ There's beauty and there's danger here ♪
♪ Split the ice apart ♪
<font color="
Come on, Sven.
Elsa. Psst!
Elsa!
Wake up. Wake up. Wake up!
Anna, go back to sleep.
I just can't.
The sky is awake, so I'm awake.
So, we have to play.
Go play by yourself.
Do you want to build a snowman?
Come on, come on, come on!
Come on!
Do the magic!
Oh...
- Ready?
- Uh-huh.
This is amazing!
Watch this!
Hi, I'm Olaf, and
I like warm hugs.
I love you, Olaf!
Olaf...
Tickle bumps!
Oh!
Hang on!
Catch me!
Gotcha!
Again!
Wait!
- Whoo-hoo!
- Slow down!
Whoo!
Anna!
Mama! Papa!
No, no...
You're okay, Anna. I got you.
Elsa, what have you done?
This is getting out of hand.
It was an accident.
I'm sorry, Anna!
- Oh. She's ice cold.
- I know where we have to go.
Ice?
Faster, Sven.
Sven!
Please! Help! It's my daughter.
It's the king.
- Trolls?
- Shush!
I'm trying to listen.
Cuties. I'm gonna keep you.
Your Majesty.
Born with the powers, or cursed?
Born.
And they're getting stronger.
Here, here.
You are lucky it wasn't her heart.
The heart is not so easily changed.
But the head can be persuaded.
Do what you must.
I recommend we remove all magic.
Even memories of magic,
to be safe.
But don't worry.
I'll leave the fun.
She will be okay.
But she won't
remember I have powers?
It's for the best.
Listen to me, Elsa.
Your power will only grow.
There is beauty in it...
But also great danger.
You must learn to control it.
Fear will be your enemy.
No!
We'll protect her.
She can learn to control it.
I'm sure.
Until then...
We'll lock the gates.
We'll reduce the staff.
We will limit her contact with people,
and keep her powers
hidden from everyone.
Including Anna.
Ah.
Elsa?
♪ Do you wanna build a snowman? ♪
♪ Come on, let's go and play ♪
<font color="
♪ Come out the door ♪
♪ It's like you've gone away ♪
♪ We used to be best buddies
And now we're not ♪
♪ I wish you would tell me why ♪
♪ Do you wanna build a snowman? ♪
♪ It doesn't have to be a snowman ♪
Go away, Anna.
♪ Okay, bye ♪
The gloves will help.
See? Conceal it.
Don't feel it.
Don't let it show.
♪ Do you wanna build a snowman? ♪
♪ Or ride our bike around the halls? ♪
♪ I think some company is overdue ♪
♪ I've started talking to
the pictures on the walls ♪
Hang in there, Joan.
<font color="
All these empty rooms ♪
♪ Just watching the hours tick by ♪
I'm scared.
It's getting stronger!
Getting upset only makes it worse.
Calm down.
No! Don't touch me!
Please, I don't wanna hurt you.
See you in two weeks!
Do you have to go?
You'll be fine, Elsa.
Your Highness.
Elsa?
♪ Please
I know you're in there ♪
<font color="
♪ They say "Have courage"
And I'm trying to ♪
♪ I'm right out here for you ♪
♪ Just let me in ♪
♪ We only have each other
It's just you and me ♪
♪ What are we gonna do? ♪
<font color="
All ashore!
Welcome to Arendelle!
Watch your step, please.
The gates will be opening soon.
Why do I have to wear this?
Because the queen has come of age.
It's Coronation Day!
That's not my fault.
What do you want, Sven?
"Give me a snack."
What's the magic word?
"Please."
Uh! Uh-uh-uh. Share.
I can't believe they're
finally opening up the gates!
- And for a whole day!
- Faster, Percy!
Arendelle, our most
mysterious trade partner.
Open those gates so I may unlock your
secrets and exploit your riches.
Did I say that out loud?
Oh! Me sore eyes can't wait to
see the queen and the princess.
I bet they are absolutely lovely.
I bet they are beautiful.
Princess Anna?
- Princess Anna?
- Huh? Yeah?
Oh. Sorry to wake you, ma'am.
No, no, no, you didn't.
I've been up for hours.
Who is it?
Still me, ma'am.
The gates will open soon.
Time to get ready.
Of course.
Ready for what?
Your sister's coronation, ma'am.
My sister's corneration.
It's Coronation Day!
♪ The window is open! ♪
♪ So's that door! ♪
♪ I didn't know they did that anymore ♪
♪ Who knew we owned
eight thousand salad plates? ♪
♪ For years I've roamed these empty halls ♪
<font color="
♪ Finally they're opening up the gates! ♪
♪ There'll be actual, real, live people ♪
♪ It'll be totally strange ♪
♪ But wow!
Am I so ready for this change! ♪
♪ 'Cause for the first time in forever ♪
<font color="
♪ There'll be light ♪
♪ For the first time in forever ♪
♪ I'll be dancing through the night ♪
♪ Don't know if I'm elated or gassy ♪
♪ But I'm somewhere in that zone ♪
♪ 'Cause for the first time in forever ♪
<font color="
I can't wait to meet everyone!
What if I meet The One?
♪ Tonight imagine me gown and all ♪
♪ Fetchingly draped against the wall ♪
♪ The picture of sophisticated grace ♪
♪ I suddenly see him standing there ♪
♪ A beautiful stranger ♪
<font color="
♪ I wanna stuff some
chocolate in my face! ♪
♪ But then we laugh and talk all evening ♪
♪ Which is totally bizarre ♪
♪ Nothing like the life I've led so far ♪
♪ For the first time in forever ♪
♪ There'll be magic
There'll be fun ♪
♪ For the first time in forever ♪
♪ I could be noticed by someone ♪
♪ And I know it is totally crazy ♪
♪ To dream I'd find romance ♪
♪ But for the first time in forever ♪
♪ At least I've got a chance! ♪
<font color="
♪ Don't let them see ♪
♪ Be the good girl ♪
♪ You always have to be ♪
♪ Conceal ♪
♪ Don't feel ♪
♪ Put on a show ♪
♪ Make one wrong move ♪
<font color="
♪ But it's only for today ♪
♪ It's only for today ♪
♪ -It's agony to wait ♪
♪ Tell the guards to open up ♪
♪ -The gate ♪
<font color="
♪ Don't let them in
Don't let them see ♪
♪ I'm getting what I'm dreaming of ♪
♪ Be the good girl ♪
♪ You always have to be ♪
♪ A chance to change my lonely world ♪
Conceal
♪ A chance to find true love ♪
<font color="
don't let them know ♪
♪ I know it all ends tomorrow ♪
♪ So it has to be today! ♪
♪ 'Cause for the first time in forever ♪
♪ For the first time ♪
♪ In forever ♪
♪ Nothing's in my way! ♪
Hey!
I'm so sorry. Are you hurt?
Hey.
Uh...
No, no, I'm okay.
Are you sure?
Yeah. I just wasn't looking
where I was going.
But I'm great, actually.
Oh... Thank goodness.
Oh! Uh...
Prince Hans of the Southern Isles.
Princess Anna of Arendelle.
"Princess"? My Lady.
Oh!
- Whoa.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa...
- Um...
- Whew.
Hi. Again.
Oh, boy!
This is awkward.
Not "You're awkward,"
but just because we're...
I'm awkward, you're gorgeous.
Wait, what?
I'd like to formally apologize
for hitting the princess
of Arendelle with my horse.
And for every moment after.
No! No, no. It's fine.
I'm not that princess.
I mean, if you had
hit my sister Elsa,
it would be... Yeesh!
Because, you know...
Hello.
But, lucky you,
It's just me.
"Just" you?
The bells. The coronation.
I better go.
I have to go. I better go. Uh...
Bye!
Oh, no. Oh!
♪  "Worthy Queen of greatness"  ♪
♪ "The heart of gold shines" ♪
♪ "We crown thee with hope, love and faith" ♪
♪ "Beautiful, stony land, home Arendelle" ♪
♪ "Follow the Queen of light." ♪
Your Majesty, the gloves.
“As she holds the holy properties,"
"And is crowned in this holy place,"
" I present to you forward…”
Queen Elsa of Arendelle.
Queen Elsa of Arendelle!
Princess Anna of Arendelle.
Oh. Here? Are you sure?
Because I don't think
I'm supposed to...
Oh. Okay.
Hi.
"Hi" me? Oh...
Um... Hi.
You look beautiful.
Thank you.
You look beautiful-ler.
I mean, not "fuller."
You don't look fuller.
But more beautiful.
Thank you.
So...
This is what a party looks like.
It's warmer than I thought.
What is that amazing smell?
Chocolate.
Your Majesty.
- The Duke of Weaseltown.
- "Weselton"!
Duke of Weselton, Your Majesty.
As your closest partner in
trade it seems only fitting
that I offer you
your first dance as queen.
One-two, and jump.
Uh...
Thank you. Only, I don't dance.
Oh...
But my sister does.
- What?
- Oh! Lucky you.
Oh, I don't think...
If you swoon, let me know.
I'll catch you.
Sorry.
Like an agile peacock.
Ow! Ow.
Speaking of, so great
to have the gates open.
Why did they shut them
in the first place?
Do you know the reason? Hmm?
- No.
All right. Hang on!
They don't call me
the "Little Dipper" for nothing!
Oh-ho!
Like a chicken with the face
of a monkey, I fly.
Let me know
when you're ready
for another round, Milady.
Well, he was sprightly.
Especially for a man in heels.
Are you okay?
I've never been better.
This is so nice.
I wish it could be
like this all the time.
Me, too.
But it can't.
- Why not?
- It just can't.
Excuse me for a minute.
I'd be honored.
Glad I caught you.
Hans.
Oop.
I often had a whole parlor
to myself to slide!
- Oh!
- Oops!
Sorry.
Your physique helps,
I'm sure, too.
Ah.
What's this?
Uh, I was born with it.
Although, I dreamed
I was kissed by a troll.
I like it.
Yeah, the whole thing.
You got it.
Okay, wait, wait.
So, you have how many brothers?
Twelve older brothers.
Three of them pretended I was
invisible, literally, for two years.
That's horrible.
It's what brothers do.
And sisters.
Elsa and I were really close
when we were little.
But then, one day,
she just shut me out,
and I never knew why.
I would never shut you out.
Okay, can I just say
something crazy?
I love crazy.
<font color="
of doors in my face ♪
♪ And then suddenly I bump into you ♪
I was thinking the same
thing, because, like...
♪ I've been searching my whole life ♪
♪ To find my own place ♪
♪ And maybe it's the party talking ♪
♪ Or the chocolate fondue ♪
<font color="
♪ But with you I found my place ♪
♪ I see your face ♪
♪ And it's nothing like
I've ever known before ♪
♪ Love is an open ♪
♪ Door! ♪
♪ - Door! ♪
<font color="
♪ Love is an open door ♪
♪ - With you ♪
♪ -With you ♪
♪ Love is an open door ♪
♪ - I mean, it's crazy ♪
- What?
♪ - We finish each other's ♪
- Sandwiches
That's what I was gonna say!
<font color="
♪ Who thinks so much like me ♪
Jinx! Jinx again!
♪ Our mental synchronisation
can have but one explanation ♪
♪ - You ♪
♪ - And I ♪
♪ - Were ♪
♪ - Just ♪
♪ Meant to be ♪
<font color="
♪ - Say goodbye ♪
♪ To the pain of the past ♪
♪ We don't have to feel it anymore ♪
♪ Love is an open door! ♪
♪ Love is an open ♪
♪ - Door! ♪
<font color="
♪ - With you! ♪
♪ Love is an open ♪
♪ - Door ♪
♪ - D-o-o-r ♪
Can I say something crazy?
Will you marry me?
Can I say something even crazier?
Yes!
- Coming through.
- Excuse me. Oh...
- Pardon. Sorry.
- Oh!
Can we just get around you there?
Thank you. Oh! There she is.
Elsa!
I mean, Queen. Me again. Um...
May I present Prince Hans
of the Southern Isles.
Your Majesty.
We would like...
Uh, your blessing...
Of our marriage.
- Marriage?
- Yes!
I'm sorry, I'm confused.
Well, we haven't worked out
all the details ourselves.
We'll need a few days
to plan the ceremony.
Of course, we'll have soup, roast
and ice cream. And then...
Wait. Would we live here?
- Here?
- Absolutely!
- Anna!
- Oh!
We can invite all 12 of your
brothers to stay with us.
What? No, no, no.
- Of course we have the room.
- Wait, slow down.
No one's brothers are staying here.
No one is getting married.
Wait, what?
May I talk to you, please? Alone.
No. Whatever you have to say,
you can say to both of us.
Fine. You can't marry
a man you just met.
You can if it's true love.
Anna, what do you know
about true love?
More than you.
All you know is how
to shut people out.
You asked for my blessing,
but my answer is no.
Now, excuse me.
Your Majesty,
if I may ease your...
No, you may not.
And I think you should go.
The party is over. Close the gates.
- Yes, Your Majesty.
- What?
Elsa, no, no! Wait.
Give me my glove!
Elsa, please, please.
I can't live like this anymore!
Then leave.
What did I ever do to you?
Enough, Anna.
No, why?
Why do you shut me out?
Why do you shut the world out?
What are you so afraid of?
I said, enough!
Sorcery.
I knew there was something
dubious going on here.
Elsa.
There she is!
Yes! It is her!
Queen Elsa.
Our beautiful queen!
Your Majesty?
Are you all right?
No.
There she is! Stop her!
Please, just stay away from me.
Stay away.
Monster. Monster!
Elsa!
Wait, please!
Elsa, stop!
Anna!
No.
The fjord.
- Snow!
- Snow?
Yes, snow.
- Are you all right?
- No.
Did you know?
No.
Look, it's snowing.
It's snowing!
The queen has cursed this land!
She must be stopped!
You have to go after her.
Wait, no!
You! ls there sorcery in you, too?
Are you a monster, too?
No, no. I'm completely ordinary.
That's right, she is.
In the best way.
And my sister is not a monster.
She nearly killed me!
- You slipped on ice.
- Her ice.
It was an accident. She was scared.
She didn't mean it.
She didn't mean any of this.
Tonight was my fault.
I pushed her.
So, I'm the one
- that needs to go after her.
- What?
- Bring me my horse, please.
- Anna, no.
It's too dangerous.
Elsa is not dangerous.
I'll bring her back,
and I'll make this right.
I'm coming with you.
No, I need you here
to take care of Arendelle.
On my honor.
I leave Prince Hans in charge.
Are you sure you can trust her?
I don't want you getting hurt.
She's my sister.
She would never hurt me.
♪ The snow glows white
on the mountain tonight ♪
♪ Not a footprint to be seen ♪
<font color="
♪ And it looks like I'm the queen. ♪
♪ The wind is howling like
this swirling storm inside ♪
♪ Couldn't keep it in,
heaven knows I tried ♪
♪ Don't let them in, don't let them see ♪
♪ Be the good girl you always have to be ♪
<font color="
don't let them know ♪
♪ Well, now they know! ♪
♪ Let it go! Let it go! ♪
♪ Can't hold it back anymore ♪
♪ Turn away and slam the door! ♪
♪ I don't care! ♪
<font color="
♪ Let the storm rage on ♪
♪ The cold never bothered me anyway! ♪
♪ It's funny how some distance ♪
♪ Makes everything seem small ♪
♪ And the fears that once controlled me ♪
♪ Can't get to me at all! ♪
<font color="
♪ To test the limits and break through ♪
♪ No right, no wrong, no rules for me ♪
♪ I'm free! ♪
♪ Let it go! Let it go! ♪
♪ I am one with the wind and sky ♪
<font color="
♪ Here I stand ♪
♪  And here I'll stay ♪
♪ Let the storm rage on! ♪
♪ My power flurries through the air
into the ground ♪
♪ My soul is spiraling in
frozen fractals all around ♪
♪ And one thought crystallises
like an icy blast ♪
♪ I'm never going back,
The past is in the past! ♪
♪ Let it go! Let it go! ♪
♪ And I'll rise like the break of dawn ♪
♪ That perfect girl is gone! ♪
<font color="
♪ In the light of day ♪
♪ Let the storm rage on! ♪
♪ The cold never bothered me anyway! ♪
Elsa!
Elsa, it's me, Anna,
your sister who didn't mean
to make you freeze the summer.
I'm sorry.
It's all my fault.
Of course, none of it
would have happened
if she had just told me her secret.
She's a stinker.
Whoa!
Oh, no. No, no, no!
Come back!
No, no, no!
Okay.
Snow. It had to be snow.
She couldn't have
had tropical magic
that covered the fjords
in white sand and warm...
Fire!
Cold, cold, cold, cold, cold.
Ooh. "And sauna"!
- Yoo-hoo.
- Hmm?
Big summer blowout.
Half off swimming suits, clogs,
and a sun balm of my
own invention, yah?
Oh. Great.
For now, um, how about boots?
Winter boots and dresses?
That would be in our
winter department.
Oh. Um...
I was just wondering.
Has another young woman...
The queen perhaps,
I don't know,
passed through here?
The only one crazy enough
to be out in this storm
is you, dear.
You and this fellow.
Yoo-hoo.
Big summer blowout.
Carrots.
Huh?
Behind you.
Oh! Right. Excuse me.
Oh. A real howler in July, yes?
Wherever could it be coming from?
The North Mountain.
North Mountain.
That will be 40.
Forty? No, 10.
Oh, dear, that's no good.
See, this is from our winter stock,
where supply and demand
have a big problem.
You want to talk about
a supply and demand problem?
I sell ice for a living.
Ooh. That's a rough business
to be in right now.
I mean, that is really...
That's unfortunate.
Still 40.
But I will throw in
a visit to Oaken's sauna.
Yoo-hoo. Hi, family.
Yoo-hoo!
Ten is all I got. Help me out.
Okay. Ten will get you
this and no more.
Okay, just tell me one thing.
What was happening
on the North Mountain?
Did it seem magical?
Yes!
Now, back up while I deal
with this crook, here.
What did you call me?
Okay, okay. I'm out.
Whoa!
Bye-bye.
No, Sven,
I didn't get your carrots.
But I did find us a place to sleep.
And it's free.
I'm sorry about this violence.
I will add a quart of lutefisk,
so we have good feelings.
Just the outfit and the boots, yah?
Uh...
♪ Reindeers are better than people ♪
♪ Sven, don't you think that's true? ♪
<font color="
and curse you and cheat you" ♪
♪ "Every one of them's bad,
except you" ♪
Aw. Thanks, buddy.
♪ But people smell better than reindeers ♪
♪ Sven, don't you think I'm right? ♪
♪ "That's once again true
For all, except you" ♪
♪ You got me
Let's call it a night ♪
♪ "Good night" ♪
♪ Don't let the frostbite ♪
♪ Bite ♪
Nice duet.
It's just you.
What do you want?
I want you to take me up
the North Mountain.
I don't take people places.
Let me rephrase that.
Hey.
Take me up the North Mountain.
Please.
Look, I know how to
stop this winter.
We leave at dawn.
And you forgot the
carrots for Sven.
Oops, sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I didn't...
We leave now. Right now.
Whew!
Hang on! We like to go fast.
- I like fast.
- Whoa! Whoa, whoa, whoa...
Get your feet down.
This is fresh lacquer.
Seriously,
were you raised in a barn?
Ugh!
- No, I was raised in a castle.
- Hmm.
So, uh, tell me,
what made the queen
go all ice-crazy?
Oh. Well...
It was all my fault.
I got engaged,
but then she freaked out,
because I'd only just met him,
you know, that day.
And she said she wouldn't
bless the marriage, and...
Wait. You got engaged
to someone you just met that day?
Yeah. Anyway, I got mad,
and so she got mad,
and then she tried to walk away,
and I grabbed her glove...
Hang on!
You mean to tell me you got engaged
to someone you just met that day?
Yes. Pay attention.
But the thing is, she wore
the gloves all the time,
so I just thought, maybe
she has a thing about dirt.
Didn't your parents ever
warn you about strangers?
Yes, they did.
But Hans is not a stranger.
Oh, yeah? What's his last name?
"Of the Southern Isles."
- What's his favorite food?
- Sandwiches.
- Best friend's name?
- Probably John.
- Eye color?
- Dreamy.
- Foot size?
- Foot size doesn't matter.
Have you had a meal with him yet?
What if you hate the way he eats?
What if you hate the
way he picks his nose?
Picks his nose?
And eats it.
Excuse me, sir.
He is a prince.
- All men do it.
- Ew.
Look, it doesn't matter.
It's true love.
- It doesn't sound like true love.
- Are you some sort of love expert?
No. But, uh,
I have friends who are.
You have friends
who are love experts?
I'm not buying it.
- Stop talking.
- No, no, no. No, no.
- I'd like to meet these...
- No, I mean it.
Sven, go.
Go!
- What are they?
- Wolves.
Wolves?
- What do we do?
- I got this.
You just...
Don't fall off, and don't get eaten.
But I want to help!
- No.
- Why not?
Because I don't trust
your judgment.
Excuse me?
Who marries a man she just met?
It's true love!
Whoa!
Whoa. Whoa!
Christopher!
It's "Kristoff"!
Ow!
Duck!
You almost set me on fire!
But I didn't.
Get ready to jump, Sven!
You don't tell him what to do.
- Hey!
- I do!
Jump, Sven!
Phew!
But I just paid it off.
Uh-oh. No. No.
No!
Ah! No, no, no, no, no, no, no!
Grab on!
Pull, Sven. Pull!
Whoa.
I'll replace your sled,
and everything in it.
And I understand if you don't
want to help me anymore.
Of course I don't want to help
her anymore. In fact,
this whole thing has ruined me
for helping anyone ever again.
It's this way?
"She'll die on her own."
- I can live with that.
- Here we go.
"But you won't get
your new sled if she's dead."
I think, actually, it's up.
Sometimes, I really don't like you.
Hold up! We're coming.
You are?
I mean, sure.
I'll let you tag along.
Arendelle.
It's completely frozen.
But it will be fine.
Elsa will thaw it.
Will she?
Yeah. Now, come on.
This way to the North Mountain?
More like this way.
I never knew winter
could be so beautiful.
Yeah.
It really is beautiful, isn't it?
But it's so white.
You know, how about a little color?
I'm thinking maybe some
crimson, chartreuse.
How about yellow?
No, not yellow.
Yellow and snow?
No go.
Am I right?
- Hi.
- You're creepy.
- Whoa!
- I don't want it.
- Back at you.
- Please don't drop me.
- No.
- Come on, it's just a head.
All right.
We got off to a bad start.
Ew, ew, ew, the body!
Wait, what am I
looking at right now?
Why are you hanging off
the earth like a bat?
All right, wait one second.
Oh. Uh...
Oh!
- Thank you.
- You're welcome.
Now, I'm perfect.
Well, almost.
It was like my whole life
got turned upside down.
Oh! Too hard. I'm sorry!
- Head rush!
- I was just... Are you okay?
Are you kidding me?
I am wonderful!
I've always wanted a nose.
So cute.
It's like a little baby unicorn.
But... Hey! Whoa!
Oh.
I love it even more.
All right, let's start this thing over.
Hi, everyone.
I'm Olaf.
And I like warm hugs.
Olaf?
That's right. Olaf.
And you are?
Oh. Um...
I'm Anna.
And who's the funky-looking
donkey over there?
- That's Sven.
- Uh-huh.
And who's the reindeer?
Sven.
Oh, the... Oh. Okay.
That makes things easier for me.
Aw, look at him
trying to kiss my nose.
- I like you, too.
- Olaf.
- Did Elsa build you?
- Yeah. Why?
Do you know where she is?
- Fascinating.
- Yeah. Why?
Do you think you could
show us the way?
Yeah. Why?
How does this work? Ow!
Stop it, Sven.
I'm trying to focus, here.
- Yeah. Why?
- I'll tell you why.
We need Elsa to bring back summer.
- Summer?
- Mmm-hmm.
Oh. I don't know why,
but I've always loved
the idea of summer.
And sun, and all things hot.
Really?
I'm guessing you don't have
much experience with heat.
Nope.
But sometimes I like
to close my eyes,
and imagine what it would be
like when summer does come.
♪ Bees'll buzz
Kids'll blow dandelion fuzz ♪
♪ And I'll be doing whatever snow does
In summer ♪
♪ A drink in my hand ♪
♪ My snow up against the burning sand ♪
♪ Prob'ly getting gorgeously tanned ♪
♪ In summer ♪
♪ I'll finally see a summer breeze ♪
<font color="
♪ And find out what happens
to solid water ♪
♪ When it gets warm ♪
♪ And I can't wait to see ♪
♪ What my buddies all think of me! ♪
♪ Just imagine how much cooler I'll be ♪
♪ In summer! ♪
♪ Da da… Da doo ♪
♪ A bah bah ba baba boo ♪
♪ The hot and the cold
are both so intense ♪
♪ Put 'em together,
it just makes sense! ♪
♪ Rat dadat dadat dadat dadadadadoo ♪
♪ Winter's a good time
to stay in and cuddle ♪
♪ But put me in summer and I'll be a... ♪
♪ Happy snowman! ♪
♪ When life gets rough ♪
♪ I like to hold on to my dream ♪
♪ Of relaxing in the summer sun
just lettin' off steam! ♪
♪ Oh the sky ♪
♪ Will be blue ♪
♪ And you guys will be there too ♪
♪ When I finally do ♪
♪ What frozen things do
in summer! ♪
- I'm gonna tell him.
- Don't you dare.
<font color="
♪ In summer! ♪
So, come on! Elsa's this way.
Let's go bring back summer!
I'm coming!
Somebody's gotta tell him.
No, no. You've got
the bark facing down.
The bark needs to be face-up.
- Bark down is drier.
- Bark up!
- Bark down!
- Papa!
Cloak? Does anyone need a cloak?
Arendelle is indebted to you,
Your Highness.
The castle is open.
There is soup and hot
glogg in the great hall.
Here, pass these out.
Prince Hans!
Are we expected
to just sit here and freeze
while you give away all
of Arendelle's tradable goods?
Princess Anna has given her orders.
And that's another thing!
Has it dawned on you that your
princess may be conspiring
with a wicked sorceress
to destroy us all?
Do not question the princess.
She left me in charge
and I will not hesitate
to protect Arendelle
from treason.
Treason?
Whoa! Whoa!
Whoa, boy. Easy.
Easy.
It's Princess Anna's horse.